compareraja.in 2014-12-19

# Privacy Policy | CompareRaja

Logicserve Digital Pvt. Ltd. is committed in respecting the privacy of every person who accesses the website [www.compareraja.in](http://www.compareraja.in/) (“Website”). Your privacy is important to us and we strive to take reasonable care and protection of the information we receive from you. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”), together with our website terms and conditions available at the link <http://www.compareraja.in/terms-conditions> sets out the basis on which we collect any personal data from you, or that you provide to us and the manner in which it will be used and processed by us. Please read the following Privacy Policy carefully to understand our practices regarding your personal data collection, usage and processing. 

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Website and not to information collected offline. By accessing the Website and providing us your information, you hereby consent to the collection and use of your information for the purposes disclosed in this Privacy Policy. You are providing the information out of your free will. If we change our Privacy Policy we will post the changes on this link. Your continued use of the Website will constitute your agreement to any such changes. 

By using/registering with the Website and by submitting your data on the Website, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. 

What information do we collect?

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

When you use or register with the Website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal and non-personal information. We may also record which products or services you are interested in as well as the webpages and links you have visited, as well as your Website usage patterns and statistics.

This information is collected to provide you with an efficient, better, customized and/or reliable services and user experience when you visit the Website as well as to improve the Website and to send you periodic emails and newsletters. 

We may collect and use your personal information to:

  * Send you, from time to time, via email or SMS, updates or news regarding the Website and its offerings, including deals of products of various vendors;
  * Transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company;
  * Send you updates or news regarding the Website and its offerings, but you may choose not to receive email of this type by using the unsubscribe option or by intimating us through email; 
  * Allow you to subscribe to our newsletters;
  * Seek your feedback or to contact you in relation to the Website and its services offered; 
  * Administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us; 
  * Anticipate and resolve problems related to the Website and its services;
  * Respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * To investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of the website or as otherwise required by law.

We may also remove all the personally identifiable information and use the rest for historical, statistical or scientific purposes.

We may additionally collect and track non-personal information about your Website visit including the domain name and the name of the web page from which you use our Website, how much time you have spent on each of our web pages, the Internet Protocol (IP) address associated with your computer, operating system and platform, transaction history, pages viewed, information searched for or requested for and other relevant statistics. We will use this information for the purposes of improving the performance and operations of our Website and its services.

How is your information protected? 

The security of your personal information is important to us. We have reasonable security measures to safeguard and protect your personal information from unauthorized access and you agree that such measures are secured and adequate. We restrict access to your personal information to our employees, agents, third party service providers, partners, banks and financial institutions as may be required who need to know such personal information in relation to the Website and its services. You agree that the security measures undertaken by such recipients (or if agreed between us and such recipients) are secured and adequate. 

While we will endeavor to take all reasonable and appropriate steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you and prevent unauthorized access, you acknowledge that the internet is not 100% secure and that we cannot provide any absolute assurance regarding the security of your personal information. We will not be liable in any way in relation to any breach of security or unintended loss or disclosure of information due to the Website being linked to the world wide web. 

Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of every minor is equally important to us. The Website is not structured to attract minor children under eighteen (18) years and you hereby acknowledge that you are above the age of eighteen (18) years while using the Website.

Do we use cookies?

Yes, we use cookies. We use cookies in order to ascertain and save your preferences for future visits and keep track of advertisements. At the same cookie date is aggregated for site traffic and site interaction in order to promote the site in a better way. Under a contract, we may approach third party service providers in order to guide us through site and the visitor traffic. The aggregate data so collected can be used by them to improve our business.

We may store cookies on your computer to collect certain information such as details about your computer, your IP address, operating system and browser type and your browsing behavior and pattern, for internal purposes and to provide you with a better Website user experience. We may also allow advertisers and other third parties to place cookies onto your computer when you visit the Website so as to show you advertisements tailored to your browsing behavior, patterns and interests, and/or to keep track of your responses to each advertisement.

You may refuse to accept cookies by deactivating the cookie option on your browser. However, if you opt for refusing to accept cookies then you may not be able to access the Website and its features properly.

Do we disclose any information to third parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to any third party your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with any law, enforce our Website policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, your non-personal identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses/purposes

However, we may disclose any or all of your personal and/or non-personal information to our group companies, affiliates or subsidiaries.

You authorize us to exchange, transfer, share, part with all information (personal and non-personal Information), across borders and from your country and jurisdiction to any other countries and jurisdictions across the world (including India), with any agent/third party service provider/partners as may be required by law, customary practice, statistical analysis, verification or risk management and shall not hold us liable for use or disclosure of this information.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. You are requested to check this section of this Website regularly. Upon updating the Privacy Policy, we may revise the "Updated" date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy.

Contact Us

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or about how we use and process your personal information, you may contact us using the information below.

Logicserve Digital Pvt Ltd  
B-201 & B-701,   
Technocity,  
Plot No. X-4/1 and X-4/2,  
Mahape, Navi Mumbai 400701

:[contact@compareraja.in](mailto:contact@compareraja.in) :022 40584508/23
